Guide to the Tamiment Library Newspapers PERIODICALS.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- The Paper Place of publication: East Lansing, Mich. Publisher: Students of Michigan State University, 1969 (Box 319)
- The Paper Place of publication: Morehead City, N.C. Publisher: Marines at Cherry Point, NC, 1971 (Box 164)
- The Paperworker Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: United Paperworkers International Union, 1972-1999 (Box 320-324)
- The Partisan Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Youth Against War and Fascism, 1970 (Box 325)
- Party Builder Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Organization Department, CPUSA, 1989 (Box 487)
- La Pasionaria Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: NYU Revolutionary Women's Community, 1971 (Box 325)
- Pax Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Chicago Peace Council, 1972-1973 (Box 325)
- Peace and Freedom News Place of publication: U.S.A. Publisher: Peace and Freedom Party, 1968-1970 (Box 325)
- Peace and Freedom Newsletter: The News from the San Francisco P & F Party Bulletins Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Peace and Freedom Party, 1969 (Box 325)
- Peace Courier Place of publication: Helsinki, Finland Publisher: Peace Courier, 1988-1993 (Box 326)
- Peace News Place of publication: London, England Publisher: Peace News Ltd., 1954-1991 (Box 328-331)
- Peace News for Nonviolent Revolution Place of publication: London, England Publisher: Peace News Ltd., 1976-1977 (Box 331)
- The Peace Times Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Vietnam Moratorium Committee, 1970 (Box 325)
- The People Place of publication: Palo Alto, Calif. Publisher: Socialist Labor Party, 1996-2008 (Box 327)
- People's Anti-War Mobilizer Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: People's Anti-War Mobilization, 1981-1983 (Box 332)
- People's Press Place of publication: Clarksville, Tenn. Publisher: G.I.s at Fort Campbell, 1971-1972 (Box 164)
- People's Tribune Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Communist Labor Party of the U.S.N.A., 1974-2013 (Box 332-335)
- People's Voice Place of publication: Edison, N.J. Publisher: American Workers Organization (Marxist-Leninist), 1973 (Box 238)
- People's Voice Place of publication: Vancouver, Canada Publisher: New Labour Press, 1998 (Box 336)
- People's Weekly World Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Long View, 2007 (Box 336)
- People's World Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Pacific Publishing Foundation, Inc., 1981 (Box 336)
- People's World (San Francisco Strike Bulletin) Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Pacific Publishing, 1948 (Box 325)
- Philly Facts Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa. Publisher: Philadelphia-TWU Local 234, 1945 (Box 411)
- Plain Speaking: A News Journal of the Democratic Workers Party Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Democratic Workers Party, 1977-1982 (Box 338)
- Plexus Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Prism Pub., 1974-1979 (Box 338)
- PM Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Newspaper PM, 1940 (Box 339)
  Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7021)
- Progressive Painter Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Inter-Local Conference of Progressive Painters, 1938-1967 (Box 343)
- Proletären Place of publication: Göteborg, Sweden Publisher: KPML(r), 1997 (Box 340)
- Public Citizen Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Public Citizen, Inc., 1976-1982 (Box 343)
- Public Employee Place of publication: Ottawa, Canada Publisher: Public Relations Dept. of the Canadian Union of Public Employees, 1978-1979 (Box 345)
- Public Employee: Official Publication, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees Place of publication: Mount Morris, Ill. Publisher: AFSCME, 1969-1985 (Box 345-346)
- Public Employee Press Place of publication: N.Y. Publisher: District Council 37, American Federation of State and Municipal Employees, 1966-2010 (Box 347-356A)
- Pulp and Paper Worker Place of publication: Fort Edward, N.Y. Publisher: Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1968 (Box 320)
- The Rag Place of publication: Austin, Tex., 1970-1971 (Box 357A)
- Rage Place of publication: Jacksonville, N.C. Publisher: By and for Marines from Camp Lejeune, 1971-1974 (Box 164)
- Rainbow People Place of publication: Gresham, Or., undated (Box 357A)
- Railroad Workers' Link Place of publication: N.Y. Publisher: Communist Party of the U.S. of A. New York (State) Railroad Committee, 1948 (Box 359)
- Rake Place of publication: Providence, R.I. Publisher: Rake Collective, 1989 (Box 357A)
- Rand School News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Rand School of Social Science, 1918-1924 (Box 357)
- Rap! Place of publication: Columbus, Ga., 1970-1971 (Box 164)
- Rat, undated (Box 477)
- The Rat Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: R.A.T. Publications, Inc., 1970-1972 (Box 357A-357B)
- Rat Subterranean News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: R.A.T. Publications, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 357A-357B)
- La Raza Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif. Publisher: La Raza, 1970 (Box 97)
- La Razón Place of publication: Amsterdam, Netherlands Publisher: C.N.T/A.I.T, 1977 (Box 28)
- Red Balloon Place of publication: Stony Brook, N.Y. Publisher: Red Balloon Collective, 1976-1985 (Box 359)
- Red Flag: Organ of the Marxist League Place of publication: London, England, 1937 (Box 359)
- Red Menace Place of publication: Toronto, Canada Publisher: Toronto Libertarian School, 1976-1979 (Box 359)
- Red Weekly Place of publication: London, England Publisher: International Marxist Group, 1973-1976 (Box 360)
- Reporter Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Legislative Conference of the City University of New York, 1971 (Box 487)
- Resistance Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: New England Resistance, 1968 (Box 360)
- Revolt Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Revolt Publishing Association, 1916 (Box 360)
- Revolutionary Age Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Left Wing Section of the Socialist Party, 1919 (Box 510)
  Researchers must use reprint volumes or microfilm (Film R-7792)
- Revolutionary Communist Youth Newsletter Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1970-1973 (Box 498)
- Revolutionary Student Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: American Student Movement (Anti-Imperialist), 1971 (Box 238)
- Revolutionary Worker Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: RCP Publications, 1979-2005 (Box 363-371)
- Revolutionary Youth Movement Newsletter Place of publication: Racine, Wis. Publisher: Revolutionary Youth Movement, undated (Box 371)
- Riff Raff Place of publication: Paris, France, 1994 (Box 372)
- Right On!: Black Community News Service Place of publication:Bronx, N.Y. Publisher: Black Panther Party, 1971-1972 (Box 373)
- Rock Creek Free Press Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: M. Sullivan, 2007-2011 (Box 371)
- Ronin, undated (Box 31)
- Rouge Place of publication: Paris, France, 1969-1987 (Box 373-373A)
  Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7222)
- San Diego Feminist Communications Place of publication: San Diego, Calif. Publisher: San Diego Feminist Communications, 1975-1978 (Box 374)
- Seafarers Log Place of publication: Camp Springs, Md. Publisher: Seafarers International Union, Atlantic, Gulf, Lakes and Inland Waters District, 1949-2014 (Box 378-381B)
- Semper Fi Place of publication: Iwakuni, Japan Publisher: GIs at MCAS Iwakuni, 1972 (Box 164)
- The Shadow Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Shadow Press, 1989-2008 (Box 028A)
- Shakedown Place of publication: Wrightstown, N.J. Publisher: Ft. Dix G.I.s, 1969-1970 (Box 164)
- Shelter Place of publication: Kansas City, Mo., 1971-1972 (Box 384B)
- Shelterforce Place of publication: East Orange, N.J. Publisher: Shelterforce Collective, 1975-1985 (Box 384B)
- Short Times Place of publication: Columbia, S.C. Publisher: GIs United Against the War in Vietnam, 1969-1971 (Box 164)
- Small Arms Place of publication: Springfield, Mass., undated (Box 477)
- SNCC Newsletter Place of publication: Atlanta, Ga. Publisher: Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee, 1967 (Box 512)
- Socialist Action Place of publication: Ann Arbor, Mich., 1973 (Box 384)
- Socialist Appeal Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Trotskyist Organizing Committee, undated (Box 436)
- Socialist Organiser Place of publication: London, England Publisher: Socialist Organiser, 1986-1990 (Box 487)
- Socialist Organiser Place of publication: London, England Publisher: Alliance for Workers' Liberty, 1985-1993 (Box 488-490)
- Socialist Organiser Place of publication: London, England Publisher: Socialist Organiser, 1991-1993 (Box 489)
- Socialist Voice Place of publication: Toronto, Canada Publisher: League for the Revolutionary Party, 1977-1978 (Box 389)
- Socialist Worker Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: International Socialist Organization, 1977-2010 (Box 389-394B)
- The Soledad Brothers Place of publication: Calif., 1971 (Box 342)
- Solidaridad obrera: órgano de la Confederación Regional del Trabajo de Cataluña: portavoz de la Confederación Nacional del Trabajo Place of publication: Barcelona, Spain Publisher: CNT-AIT, Comité Regional de Catalunya, 2007 (Box 28)
- Solidaridad obrera: supplemento literario Place of publication: Paris, France Publisher: C.N.T. d'Espagne en exil, 1959 (Box 28)
- Solidarity Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: N.Y. S.D.S. Labor Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 261)
- Solidarity / International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft & Agricultural Implement Workers of America - UAW Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: UAW, 1966-1976 (Box 438)
- Southern Patriot Place of publication: U.S.A. Publisher: Southern Conference Education Fund, 1959-1976 (Box 395)
  Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7001 and Film R-7060)
- Southern School News Place of publication: Nashville, Tenn. Publisher: Southern Education Reporting Service, 1955-1956 (Box 399)
- Southern Struggle Place of publication: Nashville, Tenn. Publisher: Southern Conference Educational Fund, 1977-1979 (Box 395)
- Spark Place of publication: Baltimore, Md. Publisher: Spark, 2002-2003 (Box 395)
- Special Weapon Place of publication: Albuquerque, N.M. Publisher: Special Weapon, undated (Box 164)
- Spectre Place of publication: Ann Arbor, Mich. Publisher: Revolutionary Lesbians, 1971-1972 (Box 399)
- Spheric Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: City College of New York, 1995-1996 (Box 111)
- Spring Movement Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Washington, Spring, 1971 (Box 399)
- Stand Up Place of publication: Eugene, Or., 1974-1981 (Box 402)
- Standard Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Henry George, 1890 (Box 513)
  Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7712)
- State and Mind Place of publication: W. Somerville, Mass. Publisher: RT, Inc., 1976 (Box 402)
- Steelabor: The Voice of the United Steelworkers of America Place of publication: Pittsburgh, Pa. Publisher: United Steelworkers of America, 1980-1984 (Box 402)
- The Storeworker: Publication of the United Storeworkers, RWDSU, AFL-CIO Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: United Storeworkers, 1969-1986 (Box 403A)
- Street Kids Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Street Kids, 1983 (Box 411)
- The Student Insurgent Place of publication: Eugene, Or. Publisher: Editorial Collective, 1990-1995 (Box 403)
- Sunburst / North American Libertarian Alliance Place of publication: Tucson, Ariz. Publisher: North American Libertarian Alliance, 1971 (Box 28)
- Survival Summer News Place of publication: Philadelphia/San Francisc, Penn./Calif. Publisher: Mobilization for Survival, 1980 (Box 111)
- Task Force Place of publication: Berkeley, Calif. Publisher: Task Force, 1968-1969 (Box 164)
- Tax Talk Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: War Tax Resistance, 1970-1975 (Box 417)
- Taxi Drivers Voice Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Taxi Drivers Union Local 3036, 1967-1997 (Box 416)
- Teacher Action Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Teachers Action Caucus of the United Federation of Teachers, 1977-1982 (Box 414)
- Teacher News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Teachers Union, 1941 (Box 289)
- The Telephone Flash Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: United Telephone Publications, Inc., 1946 (Box 415)
- Telephone Organizer / Telephone Workers Organizing Committee (C.I.O.) Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Telephone Workers Organizing Committee (C.I.O.), 1948 (Box 115C)
- Tenant Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Metropolitan Council on Housing, 1971-2014 (Box 424-425A)
- Tenants United Place of publication: Bronx, N.Y. Publisher: West Bronx Tenants Union, undated (Box 414)
- Through the Looking Glass Place of publication: Seattle, Wash. Publisher: Through the Looking Glass, 1982-1987 (Box 499)
- Tierra y Libertad Place of publication: Mexico Publisher: Tierra y Libertad, 1962-1982 (Box 28)
- Tinig-Manggagawa Place of publication: U.S.A., 1928 (Box 488)
- Today Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa. Publisher: Philadelphia Newspapers, Inc., 1972 (Box 414)
- Townsend National Weekly Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Prosperity Pub. Co., 1948-1960 (Box 405-410)
- Trade Union Action & Democracy Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: National Coordinating Committee for Trade Union Action and Democracy, 1970 (Box 414)
- Transformations Place of publication: New York, N.Y., undated (Box 432)
- Transport Bulletin (Albany-Troy Special) Place of publication: Albany, N.Y. Publisher: Transport Workers Union, 1938 (Box 412)
- Transport Bulletin (Boston Edition) Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: TWU-Local 182 CIO, 1940 (Box 412)
- Transport Bulletin (National Edition) Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Transport Workers Union of America, 1935-1942 (Box 411)
- Transport Bulletin (New York Edition) Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Transport Workers' Union, 1937-1942 (Box 413)
- Transport Bulletin (New York Weekly) Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Transport Workers Union, 1940-1941 (Box 413)
- Transport Bulletin (Philadelphia Edition) Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa. Publisher: TWU, 1937 (Box 412)
- Travisty Place of publication: Suisun City, Calif. Publisher: G.I.s at Travis Airforce Base, 1973 (Box 164)
- Tri-State Miner Place of publication: Picher, Okla. Publisher: International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, 1949 (Box 433)
- Truth Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Trotskyist Organization, USA, 1974-1985 (Box 437)
- Truth Place of publication: Oak Park, Ill. Publisher: Trotskyist Organization in the U.S., 1974-1985 (Box 437)
- Turning the Tide Place of publication: Culver City, Calif. Publisher: Anti-Racist Action Publishers, 2001-2007 (Box 357A)
- TWU Express Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Transport Workers Union of America, 1977-2005 (Box 418-422)
- UE News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America United, 1970-1991 (Box 439-442)
- Unemployed Teacher Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Unemployed Teachers Association, 1933 (Box 452)
- Union Label and Service Trades Department News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Union Label and Service Trades Department of the State of New York, 1946-1954 (Box 452)
- Union Mail Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Metro Area Postal Union, 1959-1999 (Box 453-455)
- Union Tabloid Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Graphic Arts International Union, 1983 (Box 456)
  Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7073)
- The Unionist Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Social Services Employees Union Local 371, District Council 37, AFSCME, 1969-2010 (Box 457-457A)
- Unite! Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Communist Party USA, 1975-1982 (Box 458)
- Unite Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Marxist-Leninist Organizing Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 463)
- United Rubber Worker Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1972-1988 (Box 445-446)
- The United Worker Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: United Industrial Workers, Service, Transportation, Professional & Government of North America, 1983-1988 (Box 458)
- Unity Publisher: Revolutionary Workers Movement, undated (Box 237-238)
- Up Against the Bulkhead Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Up Against the Bulkhead, 1970-1974 (Box 165)
- Up from the Bottom Place of publication: San Diego, Calif. Publisher: San Diego Area Servicemen, 1971-1974 (Box 165)
- Upstream Place of publication: Ottawa, Canada Publisher: Feminist Publications of Ottawa, 1976-1979 (Box 456)
- Utility News Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: Transport Workers Union Utility Division, 1946-1957 (Box 412)
- UTU News Place of publication: Cleveland, Ohio Publisher: United Transport Union, 1993-2002 (Box 423)
  Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7356)
- Verse Gazette Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: P. Werner, 1973 (Box 467A)
- Veterans Stars & Stripes for Peace Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Veterans for Peace, 1967-1971 (Box 165)
  Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7001 and Film R-7324)
- Vietnam Courier Place of publication: Hanoi, Vietnam, 1966-1971 (Box 465)
- Vietnam G.I. Place of publication: Chicago, Ill., 1968-1970 (Box 165)
- Vietnam Summer News Place of publication: Cambridge, Mass. Publisher: Vietnam Summer, 1967 (Box 465)
- Voice of Painters District Council 8 Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Painters, Tapers, and Paperhangers of Northern California, 1989-1991 (Box 468)
- Voice of Revolution Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: U.S. Marxist-Leninist Organization, 1986-1988 (Box 467A)
- La Voie communiste Place of publication: Paris, France Publisher: René-Boulanger, 1962 (Box 466)
- La Voz de la Alianza Place of publication: Albuquerque, N.M. Publisher: Alianza Federal de Pueblos Libres, 1970 (Box 97)
- The Wage Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Transport Workers Union, 1948 (Box 412)
- War Times Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: War Times, 2002-2006 (Box 468)
- Washington Teacher Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Washington, D.C., Teachers' Union, Local 6, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, 1984 (Box 469)
- WDL News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Workers Defense League, 1969 (Box 467)
- Western Worker Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif. Publisher: Communist Labor Party, 1974-1975 (Box 473)
- What She Wants Place of publication: Cleveland, Ohio Publisher: Cleveland Women's Counsel, 1973-1979 (Box 475)
- What the Hack Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1964 (Box 279)
- Where It's At Place of publication: West Berlin, Germany Publisher: Students for a Democratic Society in West Berlin, 1967-1968 (Box 165)
- Whig Place of publication: Angeles City, Philippines, 1971 (Box 165)
- White Collar Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Office Workers International Union, 2002 (Box 473)
- Wildcat Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Military Action Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 165)
- WiReport Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Wire Service Guild Local 222, American Newspaper Guild of New York, 1959-1989 (Box 475)
- Women and Revolution Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: The Socialist Workshop, 1971-1972 (Box 488)
- Woodhull & Claflin's Weekly Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Victoria C. Woodhull & Tennie C. Claflin, 1873 (Box 476)
  Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7793)
- The Work Force Place of publication: Albany, N.Y. Publisher: Civil Service Employees Association, 2006-2010 (Box 477A)
- The Worker, 1979 (Box 371)
- The Worker Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Long View Publishing Company, 1968 (Box 478)
- The Worker for the Bay Area Place of publication: Oakland, Calif. Publisher: Revolutionary Communist Party, USA, 1975-1978 (Box 482)
- The Worker for the Bay Area and Salinas Valley Place of publication: Oakland, Calif. Publisher: Revolutionary Communist Party, USA, 1978-1979 (Box 482)
- Workers' Action Place of publication: Emeryville, N.Y. Publisher: Committee for a Labor Party, 1968-1971 (Box 479)
- The Workers' Advocate Place of publication: Cleveland, Ohio Publisher: American Communist Workers Movement, 1969-1970 (Box 238)
- Workers' Advocate: Voice of the Marxist-Leninist Party of the USA Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Marxist-Leninist Publications, 1977-1993 (Box 479-481)
- Workers' Power Place of publication: Highland Park, Mich. Publisher: International Socialist Publishing Company, 1971-1976 (Box 501)
- Workers' Unity Place of publication: London Publisher: LinkLondon: South African Congress of Trade Unions, 1978 (Box 491)
- Workers Vanguard Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Spartacist Pub. Co., 2001-2010 (Box 455-455B)
- World Revolution Place of publication: London, England Publisher: World Revolution, 1981-1993 (Box 505)
- World War III Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: A.E. Melton, 1969 (Box 503)
- WREE-View: Bulletin of Women for Racial and Economic Equality Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: WREE, 1977-1981 (Box 506)
- Writing Place of publication: Vancouver, Canada Publisher: Georgia Straight Pub., 1970 (Box 506)
- Y.C.L. News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Council, Young Communist League, 1941-1942 (Box 513)
- Yellow Journal Place of publication: Vancouver, Canada Publisher: Pressgang Publishers, 1970 (Box 506)
- Young Progressive Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Young Progressives of America, 1948 (Box 499)
  Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7484)
- Young Socialist Place of publication: London, England, undated (Box 436)
- Young Spartacus Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Spartacus Youth Publishing Co., 1982-1986 (Box 498)
- Young Worker Publisher: Young Workers League, 1967-1968 (Box 499)
- Young Worker Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Young Workers Liberation League, 1970-1983 (Box 499)
- Young Worker: Official Organ of the Young Workers League Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Organization Committee for the Young Workers League of America, 1929-1930 (Box 499)
  Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7697)
- Your Military Left Place of publication: San Antonio, Tex. Publisher: G.I. Anti-war, 1972 (Box 165)
- Youth Action for Socialism: Organ of the National Provisional Committee for a Socialist Youth League Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Provisional Committee for a Socialist Youth League, 1945 (Box 499)